(Sheldon:)Did he mean
as if she'd been out in the sun,
(Sheldon:)tending an herb garden without
wearing a hat or sunblock?
(Dr. Brian Greene:)No.
(Leonard:)That's not what he meant.
(Sheldon:)Well, we may never know.
(Sheldon:)As my mother would say,
(Sheldon:)the Asians are
an inscrutable folk.
(Sheldon:)Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you do.
You dog, you.
(Sheldon:)Did you get that?
(Amy(on webcam):)Every word.
(Amy(on webcam):)Our false gossip meme appears
to have reached node lambda.
(Sheldon:)This is moving faster
than we thought.
(Sheldon:)Agreed.
(Amy:)It appears the rate
(Amy:)of gossip transmission
(Amy:)is proportional
to the number of nodes squared.
(Sheldon:)I must say, Amy,
(Sheldon:)pretending
to have intercourse with you
(Sheldon:)is giving me
a great deal of satisfaction.
(Amy:)Slow down, Sheldon.
I'm not quite there yet.